Ct.
I am Ikeda, a 5th term student
I'm Okuromi, a 4th term student.
Please do me a favor.
Actually, I'll be at the Hong Kong concert this time.
Yes, that's right.
We've arrived in Hong Kong.
We've arrived.
Actually, there's somewhere I really want to go.
Where?
I've always dreamed of seeing a panda.
Is that why you're doing the patsa?
Yes, sir.
He's cute.
So cute!
I'm going to put on my pampas.
Yay!
Thank you for your hard work.
I thought I'd go discover the real Teresa Panda.
This place is called Ocean Park.
It's an aquarium, zoo and amusement park.
It's an aquarium, a zoo and an amusement park.
And of course, you can see pandas there...
You can see the pandas, of course, but you can also get up close to them.
I heard that there's also that kind of experience.
I thought it would be a good place for me to visit.
I came to Ocean Park.
Yay!
I'm excited. I'm happy.
You wanna go?
We'll go together. What's that? We found a telepanda?
I'd like to go with you.
Are you sure?
I found Teresa Panda.
Oh, my God, I'm so happy.
That's great.
That's hot.
It's really big.
Great, great, great theme park music.
So happy to see so many people.
There's so much delicious food!
Wow, it looks so good!
There's chicken and potatoes, too!
I can't believe it!
There's even a ropeway over there!
It's amazing how far up the mountain it is!
You've been here before, right?
Yes, I have.
It's not like we do that many panda experiences.
It's been so long I don't remember.
So you're saying it's a bit rare today?
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, there's a panda.
There are pandas.
I'll go over there.
Wow...
There's a lot of tele-fans.
He's kind of handsome.
He's a little bit handsome.
There are so many pandas!
The Great Bear Cat's Journey: A Diant Panda Adventure
Amazing!
Ohonmachi Yui Dianto Panda Adventure
Yes, it's great!
It says "Roshan Park" right?
I'm so excited!
Hey...
It looks like an amazing cave.
Yeah, it is.
There's a map.
Look.
Where is it?
Amazing!
That's it... right there, top left... the main room.
A panda.
Kitty.
There's a red panda, too. That's great.
Let's go.
Hello.
Oh, my God.
So cute.
There are many more.
Pandas and red pandas.
Amazing.
Sparkling!
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
It's all opening up at once.
Wait, is it coming out?
He's doing the leaner.
He's eating the main course.
Great, great, great, great, great, great.
Is he eating it all at once?
Oh, my God.
I wonder if he'll notice if I wave.
Hey!
He's into the bamboo grass.
They don't notice me at all.
Restaurant bread!
Restaurant!
They're outside the restaurant!
He's so cute!
Siphon man.
Hey, guys.
They don't even know we're here.
Will you look at me?
He's so service-oriented.
Oh, my God.
Here they come. Here they come. Here they come.
He's coming so fast.
He's a panther god!
Panther gods!
Yeah, let's get a shot too!
Yay!
Oh, and you can see my butt!
Butt, butt, butt!
A panda.
So there's another one.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, there it is.
You got your clothes on!
I got you, I got you, I got you, I got you, I got you.
Wait, I should've gotten that face right.
It's a little too much. It's sunny...
I wonder if he's sleeping...
I'm up, I'm up, I'm up!
I'm too much like I was when I slept until this afternoon.
So cute, so cute, so cute!
Oh, no, it's too much treasure!
I'm still squishy!
I'm doing pandas right now... but I've come all the way to Hong Kong to have my first memories of pandas...
I've prepared a plan to make our first panda experience together a memorable one.
What? Can I make an announcement? Yes! Kurumi.
I've made reservations to feed the pandas.
You can feed the pandas?
I found out that you have to make a reservation to feed the pandas.
I was thinking that I would like to feed the pandas and have them do it, so I made a reservation.
I'm so glad!
I was able to negotiate with them to let me feed the pandas.
Thank you so much!
I'm looking forward to it.
I got to meet a panda for the first time in my life, and I got to feed him.
That's amazing!
I love Japanese weddings.
I'm so happy!
We did it!
So let's go feed the panda and make some great memories!
Let's go!
Now we're going to lead the pandas to here.
What?
You're going to feed them here already?
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. Are you ready?
Cute.
LALA.
Boy.
I finally found the real one. I found Teresa Panda.
Here we go.
Oh, thanks for the ride.
I'm in.
He's not chewing as hard as you'd think.
He's eating like a champ.
Delicious?
He's making a face like it's Fren's time.
Mr. Kuromi.
You're a panda now, aren't you?
I'm so happy.
That was amazing.
It was the first time in my life I found a panda.
How was it?
I didn't expect to be allowed to feed it.
The power of the black world...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He was so cute.
He was eating so deliciously.
I was getting a craving too.
Are you hungry?
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry, too.
Really?
Let's see if we can find something.
Sure.
Always.
Is there anything you eat when you come to Hong Kong?
I always have to start with an iced lemon tea.
Iced lemon tea?
Yeah, I'm having some right now.
It's pretty sweet.
Oh, yeah.
There's a lot to choose from, isn't there?
I'm so excited.
I can't read what it says.
If you could just read it and let me know, that would be great.
Something tasty, something you'd like to try?
What about this?
What's this?
Is this it?
Daguchi suas долго.
Gaidanjan?
It comes in a variety of flavors.
It's a little bit like baby katsura.
Sounds yummy!
That's why it says pancakes.
It's true.
I'd like to try it.
Okay, sure.
But I think the milk is too much.
But it's good if you get three different flavors like this.
You're right.
You can get it?
Let's order it then.
Hello!
Hey!
Gaidanjan?
Gaidan jin?
Okay.
And cash?
Let's say 50.
That's not quite right.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you.
What does it taste like?
It smells so good.
Oh, that sounds delicious.
What would you like?
Iced milk tea?
Yes, sir.
Iced, right?
Yes, iced.
Okay, then.
I'm all alone now.
Telepan is waiting for me.
I'll do my best to act like a senior.
I don't know.
Milk tea? I'm gonna miss it.
Hello.
I'll get you some Byango ice cream.
Ice cream.
Ice cream, yes.
Yes, this way
Oh, Kurami-san bought it. I'm so glad.
I think I'll eat it.
It says "pancake" on it.
It's not so obvious even if I taste just a little.
It's delicious.
Ah, telefan.
Telefan.
I left it with you.
Wait a minute. What is it? What's this?
Iced milk tea.
Oh, we talked earlier.
Did you buy it?
I did.
Sold.
Please come in.
I'll start with the iced milk tea you bought.
Cheers.
Bon appétit.
Delicious!
It's so good!
Oh, thank God.
It's too good.
Okay, here you go.
Okay, you can start with the televan.
Eat, eat, eat.
The one Mr. Kuromi ordered for us earlier.
Gaidanjan.
Baby sponge cake.
In the shape of a mash.
Like this.
Looks delicious!
It's like this.
It's all connected together like this.
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Yum.
What's it like?
It's like a baby sponge cake.
But I was wondering about something.
There were chocolate, condensed milk and strawberry flavors, right?
I think I forgot to get those.
Does that mean I can get them if I ask?
I think I can get them if I ask.
Can we go get them again?
Wanna go?
Let's go.
But you have to taste this plain.
Yes, sir.
It's easy.
Yes, it's good.
Yum.
It's probably not all three flavors.
Let's go with this one.
But I don't know if it's right.
Just say I'm sorry if I'm wrong.
Get that one.
You mean 38?
Maybe.
Maybe you can get me some condensed milk.
I'd like to have some.
Excuse me.
She understands.
Good.
It means you can choose.
Even anyway.
I got it.
Yay!
It was milk.
It's like condensed milk.
Thank you.
Is it good?
It's umaike-da.
Umaikeda?
There's umaike-da, too?
Umaiyoki no pacri.
Delicious!
Mmm.
Mnh-mnh.
Delicious!
Even if you don't put anything on it...
Of course it's delicious, but it tastes sweeter with it.
Mm-hm-hm-hm.
It's delicious.
It goes well with iced milk tea.
That was good.
It was good.
No, it was delicious.
The angle of this picture is really cool. The sunlight is really cool.
Oh, the shadows. Shadows, yay!
Wow, you can see this area.
Is this a souvenir road?
I want a panda.
I want to buy matching pandas.
I want to buy one.
Where are all the pandas?
Let's just go in.
Should we start here?
What do you want?
That's the one from before.
That's Rin-chan.
Here, here, here.
This is the bottom one.
That's the bottom one mixed in.
Tamami gave us these sweets.
Tamami gave me.
That or the photo book?
It's a souvenir from the bookstore.
He told me to eat the panda.
I can't choose any more.
I'm going to buy so many pandas!
Oh, no...
What... what... what...
Oh, my gosh!
So many stuffed animals!
I'd like to buy one, even though I said I'd lose if I bought a bunch of stuffed animals.
Then give me this!
They're matching pouches!
I've been wanting one.
Really? I'm so happy!
I don't even know what a stuffed mussel is, but it's so cute.
I'll buy it and go home.
Okay, by the way...
The sky is getting darker.
It all happened so fast.
How was it?
I left Japan for the first time in my life
I came to Hong Kong for the first time in my life.
I was able to meet and feed the pandas.
I was able to meet and feed the pandas, and I really discovered the pandas.
I was escorted by a nice senior staff member.
I loved Ocean Park and
I love Ocean Park and Mr. Krame even more!
Here you are!
So cute!
Yay!
I couldn't escort him yet, but...
It was so cool!
But it was so much fun!
It's not often that I get to make memories with the members overseas.
It was the first time in my life.
That's right.
It was a very deep memory for me.
I'll never forget it.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Bye bye!
Joy Joy
Next Episode